austinisd.org 2019-12-02

# Privacy Policy | Austin ISD

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, austinisd.org collects non-personally identifying information that users typically make available to web browsers and servers , such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. The purpose of austinisd.org collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how visitors use its website, and to make for a better experience for the public. From time to time, Austin ISD may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. Austinisd.org also collects potentially personally identifying information such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Austin ISD does not use such information to identify its visitors and does not disclose such information.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to austinisd.org choose to interact with the website in ways that require them to provide personally identifying information. The amount and type of information the website gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, the district asks visitors who use contact forms to provide a phone and email address. In each case, austinisd.org collects such information only as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with the website.

## Protection of Certain Personally Identifying Information

Austin ISD will not rent or sell potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information to anyone.

If you are a registered user of an Austin ISD newsletter and have supplied your email address, the district may occasionally send you an email requesting your feedback and keeping you up-to-date with district information. Austinisd.org takes all necessary measures to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally identifying.

## Aggregated Statistics

Austinisd.org may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, austinisd.org may reveal how many times specific documents were downloaded, or which pages are most popular.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Austinisd.org uses cookies to help identify visitors, their usage of the website, and their website access preferences. Austinisd.org visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers can opt out below, or should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using austinisd.org’s websites. Certain features of austinisd.org’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Opt-Out of Website Tracking

## Privacy Policy Changes

Austinisd.org may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at Austin ISD’s sole discretion. Austin ISD encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any changes in this privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
